My lord, why are you still awake so late at night?
The servants reported seeing
a maid wandering the manor late at night
and brought her in for questioning
How has my wife been doing lately?
The princess consort is perfectly well
Do you have a lover in this household?
What kind of scheme is Zhu Huaichen up to?
My lover is Ah Huang, the kitchen boy
Wait
Why is Huashan acting so strangely today?
Why would she say these things?
Then what about the money and deed found on you?
How do you explain that?
The money and deed were given to me by the princess consort
I can't let him keep questioning her
The princess consort thought my cooking was excellent
so she granted me freedom to open a food stall
She even promised to paint for me
My lord, this is all my fault
I should have discussed this with you
I privately gave Huashan her deed of servitude
I thought she was skilled and young
If she could open her own eatery outside
she would surely have a bright future
and free her descendants from servitude
You wouldn't blame me, would you, my lord?
My wife is so kind-hearted
Of course I wouldn't blame you
Huashan
Huashan, you may leave now
Let me explain to my lord
My lord has always been exceptionally kind to servants
Surely he wouldn't make things difficult for Huashan
Isn't this the maid the princess usually interacts with?
Huashan... Now I remember
The Western Envoy once gave Zhu Huaichen a Truth-Telling Gu
They say whoever is infected by this gu
must answer any question asked
and must answer truthfully
Zhu Huaichen
You're truly despicable
What is that?
Blood
It's the smell of blood
Assassins!
Huashan is dead
Assassins! My lord, run!
Imperial Brother
The whereabouts of the Dragon Jade remain unknown
We must stop listening to the slander of villains
To avoid arousing Li Zhi'an's suspicion
It wasn't his idea
All because of you
But now it's fine
Tested the gu worms - they're indeed effective
Once the old Li faction surrenders
Obtaining the Dragon Jade will be as easy as taking something from a bag
You won't have to
Be a substitute anymore
Zhi'an
Zhi'an, wake up
Zhi'an... Zhi'an...
Huashan
Zhu Huaichen is ruthless, treating human lives as worthless as grass
He's becoming increasingly deranged
I must quickly contact the remaining members of the Li family
Imperial Consort
The Grand Princess has gone to Nanshan for spiritual cultivation
That Nanshan is located at the border between Nanliang and Beijin
It's a long journey
I'm afraid this token won't reach her hands
It seems I won't be able to meet her anytime soon
What about Hualan?
Hualan has already taken her certificate of freedom and returned home
She took Huashan's remains with her
It's good that she left
Li Zhi'an is clearly so suspicious
Why hasn't the Seventh Prince taken action against her yet?
And he keeps compromising his plans for her repeatedly
Even though he's been planning for so long
Isn't it obvious?
He's not doing it because he doesn't want to
The Seventh Prince
has feelings for Li Zhi'an
I won't let anyone interfere with his ascension to the throne
You'd better not make any unnecessary moves
The Seventh Prince has his own plans
Li Zhi'an
Let's see how you'll manage
to escape this Truth Worm nourished with my blood
Once you swallow this worm
you won't be able to hide the whereabouts of the Dragon Jade Treasure
Once we obtain the treasure
you'll become expendable
Steward Duan dismissed the servants
Do you wish to discuss something with me?
This is the newly bestowed Yangchun wine from His Majesty this year
I brought it especially for the Princess Consort to taste
Now that she's under Zhu Huaijin's command
Could it be Zhu Huaijin sent her to plant a worm in me?
The Princess Consort has impaired vision
Let me assist you
Steward Duan, why does this wine smell foul?
Has something unclean contaminated it?
Let me get you another cup
This is newly poured wine
It definitely shouldn't smell foul
If you still refuse to drink this imperial wine
I'll begin to suspect
it's not your sense of smell that's the problem
but something else entirely